Joined in body, soul… and murder
Sisters is a mystery, thriller, horror film directed by Douglas Buck.
A reporter witnesses a brutal murder and becomes entangled
in a mystery involving a pair of twins.
Grace Collier, played by Chloë Sevigny.
Dr. Philip Lacan, played by Stephen Rea.
Angelique Tristiana, played by Lou Doillon.
Dr. Dylan Wallace, played by Dallas Roberts.
Larry Franklin, played by JR Bourne.
Dr. Lucas Bryant, played by William B. Davis.
Sisters is a 2006 American psychological horror film directed by Douglas Buck and starring Stephen Rea, Lou
Doillon, and Chloë Sevigny, with Dallas Roberts and JR Bourne playing supporting characters.
A remake of the 1972 Brian De Palma film of the same name, it follows a journalist who becomes embroiled in a
criminal investigation after witnessing a woman's disturbed twin sister commit a violent murder.
Principal photography of Sisters took place largely
in Vancouver in the spring of 2006.
The film premiered at the Sitges Film Festival on October 13, 2006, with subsequent screenings
at several film festivals in late 2006 and 2007, including South by Southwest.
In the United States, the film was released
directly to DVD by Image Entertainment.
The film explores themes of psychotic, absurd, depressing, bewildered.
The tone is intense and dark and mind_bending.